字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：王大可 Reginamoon 小暴徒 想名字好难 木浅薰
翻译：Timothy dzysteven sylvia  校对：油炸电风扇   木浅薰
时间轴：壬虚浪影  倩倩  Spohy
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第二集
《诉讼双雄》前请提要
-罗伯特・赞恩向你发出了邀请  -是的
- Robert Zane made you an offer. - He did.
你求我再给你一次机会
You begged me for a second chance.
现在他是要利用你摧毁我们
And now he's using you to destroy us.
你步伐轻盈地走进来以为这会跟
You waltzed in here thinking this was gonna be
监狱电影的桥段一样  然而现实并非如此
like some prison movie, but it's not.
-这里就是监狱  -欢迎来到丹伯里
- It's just prison. - Welcome to Danbury.
-迈克・罗斯  -弗兰克・加洛
- Mike Ross. - Frank Gallo.
我们因为迈克・罗斯接触过的所有案子被告了
We're being sued for every case Mike Ross has ever touched.
你不想承认这整件事都是
You won't admit this whole thing is your fault
-因你的错而起  -我的错吗
- in the first place. - My fault?
要不是我把迈克招进来  你到现在
If I hadn't brought Mike in, you'd still be here
还只能跟个初级合伙人一样
sniveling around like a Goddamn junior partner.
你的未婚妻  你想打给她吗
Your fiancé, you want to call her?
也许我该给瑞秋发条短信
Maybe I'll just send Rachel a text.
我们得在明天之前转移
We need to move the money that we have
所有账户里的钱
in every account by tomorrow.
我们用不着转移
We don't need to move it.
我们得利用它们  和解公司所面临的集体诉讼
We can use their buy-ins to settle the class-action lawsuits.
好了  走吧
All right, let's go.
这就是我的牢房  你们给我的牢房
I'm in the right cell. I'm in the one you gave me.
是啊  但这不是他们给我的房间
Yeah, but this isn't the one they gave me.
你说你本来你可以让另一个人进来的
You said you could've turned on a guy to get out of here,
但是你没有  因为你觉得自己亏欠他
but you didn't because you owe him.
好吧  我也欠那个狗娘养的
Well, I owe that son of a bitch too.
-混蛋  -放松  迈克
- You son of a bitch. - Take it easy, Mike.
记得我知道你的一切
And remember, I know about you.
还有你女朋友的电话号码
And I got your little girlfriend's number right here.
你一直盯着表看
You keep watching that clock,
那你的两年会很漫长
it's gonna be a long two years.
不管你相不相信  我也曾经像你这样
Believe it or not, I've been where you are right now.
你整晚都在想着如何
You've been thinking about how to get back
能报复那个混蛋
at that son of a bitch all night.
向他的燕麦粥吐口水
Spit in his oatmeal.
在他的枕头上拉屎
Shit on his pillow.
不论你有什么想法  我的建议就是不要做
Whatever it is, my advice to you is don't do it.
我不需要你的建议
I don't need any advice from you.
-你说什么  -就是你
- Excuse me? - You're the one
让我和那个神经病待在一起的
that left me alone with that psychopath in the first place.
现在我明白你为什么
Now I get why you haven't
整晚都没有跟我讲话了
said a word to me since last night.
发生了这种事
How the hell did you think I'd react
-你认为我该有什么反应  -听着  伙计
- after something like that? - Hey, listen, man.
我跟你没有任何过节
I don't have anything against you,
但我们之间也没有任何交情
but I sure as hell don't have anything for you.
我当然不会为了一个陌生人
And I'm not gonna cause trouble with a guy like that
去招惹那样一个人  所以如果他想
for someone I've never even met, so if he wants me
让我换几个小时的房间  那我就换
to switch for a few hours, I'm switching.
才不管我会发生什么呢  是吧
To hell with what happens to me, right?
-我可没这么说  -你只是这么做了
- Hey, I didn't say that. - No, you just did it.
唐娜  你来干什么
Donna, what are you doing here?
我来送礼物的
I come bearing gifts.
非常感谢  但你不用特地跑来这里看我
That's really nice, but you don't have to come over here
我没事
to check on me. I'm fine.
你可是穿着你未婚夫的衬衫在说这些话
Says the girl in her fiancé's shirt.
听着  我知道这有点俗气
Look, I know it's cheesy.
瑞秋  你想感受到他就在你身边
Rachel, you wanted to feel him next to you.
这并不俗气
It's not cheesy.
谢谢  唐娜
Thanks, Donna.
你确实该谢谢我
Well, you do owe me a thank you,
但不是因为这件事
but it's not for that.
因为过几个小时
Because in a couple of hours it's going to be more
就不止他的衬衫围绕着你了
than his shirt wrapped around you.
你是说你把我加到探访名单了
Are you saying that you got me on the visitor's list,
但他们说如果不是家属
because they said that if I'm not family--
我不在乎他们怎么说  你就是他的家属
I don't care what they said. You're his family.
你也是我的家人  昨晚不把你弄到名单上
And you're my family, and I wasn't going to sleep last night
我是睡不着的
until I got you on that list.
我不知道该说什么好了
I-I don't know what to say.
说"谢谢你  唐娜"  然后去看他
Say, "Thank you, Donna," and get your ass up there.
你手里拿着什么呢  猛男
What you got in your hand there, tiger?
深度烘焙  加奶油  不加糖
Dark roast, splash of cream, no sugar.
为什么对我这么好
And to what do I owe the honor?
我今早在想你把我
I was thinking this morning about the day
从收发室选出来的那天
you picked me out of the mailroom
-到现在已经发生了多少事  -可笑的是
- and how far we've come. - You know, it's funny.
我今早在想的是到现在我们已经堕落了多深
I was thinking this morning about how far we've fallen.
那就让我们结束这些诉讼吧
Then let's go put these lawsuits to bed.
不好意思  警官
Excuse me, Officer?
我知道电话十点后才能用
I know the phones don't open until 10:00,
但我想问一下是否能
but I was wondering if it's possible for me
让我现在打个电话
to make a phone call?
站回队里  吃你的早餐
Get back in line and eat your breakfast.
求你了  我这么说的唯一原因
Please. The only reason I'm asking
是有紧急事件  我只需要
is 'cause it's an emergency. I just need a little--
怎么了  你着火了吗
What, are you on fire?
你的腿摔折了
Your leg broken?
因为在我看来你是想打电话给外面的人
'Cause it looks to me like you're trying to call
说一些你在这里面的事情
someone out there about something that happened in here.
你不明白  好吧  我的未婚妻
You don't understand, all right, my fiancé is--
不  是你不明白
No, you don't understand.
除非是有炸弹要爆炸了
Unless there's a bomb headed for us,
外面的任何事情都跟
nothing that happens out there has anything to do
这里面的事无关了  明白了吗
with what happens in here. You got that?
好的  明白了
Yeah, got it.
我昨晚走的很匆忙
Hey, I left in such a hurry last night,
没来得及跟你道别
didn't get a chance to say good-bye.
那我现在说
Well, I'll say it now.
好好生活  别招惹我
Have a nice life. Leave me alone.
你不想看看你未婚妻
Don't you want to see a copy of the pictures
昨晚给我发的照片吗
your fiancé sent me last night?
你放屁  她没给你发任何东西
That's bullshit. She didn't send you anything.
你说对了  她没给我发
You're right, she didn't.
她是发给你的
She sent 'em to you.
我是说  本来就是你先开始的
I mean, you're the one who started it all,
告诉她你有多想她
telling her how much you missed her.
你认为在那之后我让她
How hard do you think it was for me to get her
给我发张性感照片能有多难
to send a sexy picture to you after that?
好像现在的孩子们管那叫自拍
I think that kids today call it a selfie.
她不可能给你发那种照片
There's no way she sent you a picture like that.
你说对了  并不性感
You're right, it wasn't sexy.
我做了什么呢  我把她的脸
But what I did, I photoshopped her face
拼接到了一个性感身体上
onto a body that is.
我弄得可好了
I did such a good job,
这里的人都发现不了
no one in here is ever gonna notice.
是啊  我还弄了好多份
Yeah. I made copies.
这里的每个人都有一份
One for each guy in the joint.
一般这种情况我都是要收费的
Usually, a situation like this, I would charge a fortune.
但今天我心情好
But today, I'm feeling so generous
我打算免费发给他们
I'm going to give them away for free.
别纠缠他了  加洛
Get off him, Gallo!
什么  我什么都没做  是他攻击我
What? I didn't do shit! He attacked me!
那是放屁
That is bullshit!
我之前就是想和你说就是这个人
I tried to tell you that's the guy.
我不在乎你之前想干什么
I don't care what you tried to do.
你不是说有紧急情况嘛  现在是有了
You wanted an emergency, now you got it.
-把他俩都带出去  -什么
- Get 'em both out of here. - What?
早上好  皮尔逊女士  斯佩克特先生
Good morning, Ms. Pearson, Mr. Specter,
两位需要热毛巾吗
can I offer either of you a hot towel?
小姐  能否麻烦你告诉我是谁雇的你
Miss, would you mind telling me who hired you?
我觉得我俩都心知肚明
I think we both know who hired her.
你小子在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
-我在复印  -滚犊子
- I'm making copies. - Goddamn it.
我们付你350一小时不是请你来复印的
We don't bill you out at 350 an hour to make copies.
快给我滚回去工作
Now get your ass back to work.
那份动议可不会自己起草好
That motion isn't going to file itself.
路易  你干了什么
Louis, what the hell did you do?
什么  你在说什么
What? What are you talking about?
我们没钱雇律师
We don't have the money to hire associates,
律师助理  或者客服人员
paralegals, and support staff.
我知道
I know that.
我不是白痴  他们不是客服人员
I'm not an idiot, they're not support staff.
那他们是什么人
Who the hell are they?
他们是临时演员
They're movie extras.
你昨晚飞了多少叶子
How much weed did you smoke last night?
我们一小时后就要进行和解谈判了
We have a settlement meeting in an hour.
假如他们走进来时看到这些办公室都是空的
And if these offices are empty when they walk in,
我们就会非常难堪了
we are gonna look like shit.
路易  你有没有意识到
Louis, did it occur to you
我们在谈判中要威胁他们说我们要破产了
that we're using the threat of bankruptcy in that meeting,
而假如这些办公室都是满的
and if these offices are filled,
我们的计划就失效了
it kills that plan?
所有人立刻放下手中的活儿
Everybody drop whatever the hell it is you're doing
然后把你们的工作时间记录卡交给我秘书
and hand your timecards in to my secretary.
假如迟了一秒钟
And if they are marked one second late,
我向上帝发誓
I swear to God,
你再也不能在这座城市假扮律师了
you will never be fake associates in this town again.
下一位
Next.
-你好  -犯人姓名
- Hi. - Inmate's name?
迈克・罗斯  我是来探视的
Mike Ross. I'm here for visitation.
看来罗斯先生今天不能见访客
It appears Mr. Ross is not receiving visitors today.
我...我不明白
I-I don't understand.
我听说我是在获批访客名单上的
I was told that I was on the approved visitors list.
这里说是因为他今早的斗殴行为
It says visitation has been suspended for two weeks
两周内暂时不能接受探视
because of an altercation he had this morning.
不  不可能  他昨天才刚到这里
No, that can't be right. He just got here yesterday.
有可能  而且事实就是如此
It can be right, and it is right.
那么我需要马上见到他
Well then, I need to see him right away.
我刚刚才告诉你你不能见他
And I just told you you can't do that.
我可以  因为我不但是他的未婚妻
Yes, I can. Because not only am I his fiancé,
我还是他的律师
I'm also his lawyer.
这里写着他的律师是哈维・斯佩克特
It says here a Harvey Specter is his lawyer.
他是皮尔斯-斯派克特-利特律所的  我也是
And he works at Pearson, Specter, Litt, and so do I.
名片上写着律师助理
This card says paralegal.
我不在乎上面写着什么
I don't care what it says.
假如你不让我进去  然后他出事了
You don't let me in there and something's wrong with him,
我这辈子的目标就会是让你生不如死
I will make it my life's purpose to make your life a living hell.
女士  我干这行干了十年了
Ma'am, I worked maximum security for ten years,
所以如果你觉得我会被你这种人威胁
so if you think I'm gonna be intimidated by the likes of you,
你就大错特错了
you've got another thing coming.
一般来说犯人进来几周后才会第一次违规
You know, usually it takes prisoners a couple of weeks to get their first violation.
你来这里还不到24小时
You've been here less than 24 hours.
可能都破纪录了
That might just be a record.
行了  我不在乎  我需要打个电话
Yeah, I don't care. I need to make a phone call.
在你刚刚的所作所为之后  你什么也不能干
You're not making anything after what you just did.
我什么也没干  是他陷害我
I didn't do anything. He set me up.
我不在乎他干了什么
I don't care what he did.
所以你说的那堆帮我成为 "更好的我"
So all that stuff about you helping me become a "better version" of myself,
都是在放屁吗
that was bullshit?
-不  不是  -那你到底是什么意思
- No, it wasn't. - Then what exactly did you mean?
因为如果连我的说法你都不听
Because if you won't even hear my side of the story,
那你要怎么帮我
then how are you gonna help me?
好吧  你说他陷害你是什么意思
All right, what do you mean he set you up?
我的意思是  他收买了警卫
I mean, he paid off a guard,
然后他装作是我的室友
then he posed as my roommate,
接下来他就打算把我未婚妻的照片
and the next thing I know, he's about to hand out pictures of my fiancé
发给这整座监狱里的所有犯人了
to every inmate in this entire prison.
没有证据显示有什么照片
There's no evidence of any pictures.
那些照片不是撒了一地吗
But they were all over the floor.
这就是撒了一地的东西
This is what was all over the floor.
听我说  也许的确没有证据
Listen to me, there might not be any proof,
但我告诉你  他收买了一个警卫
but I am telling you that he paid off a guard
而你需要对此采取一些行动
and you need to do something about it.
兄弟  我无权管那些警卫
Brother, I don't have any authority over the guards.
那我到底在这里干什么
Then what exactly am I doing here?
你在学习如何在不使情况恶化的前提下
You are learning how to deal with the bullshit life throws your way
处理生活对你的蹂躏
without making your situation worse.
我他妈要怎样才能做到那一点
And how the hell am I supposed to do that?
这可不是茶会
This isn't just a tea party.
这次谈话的目的是观察你是否值得被改造
The purpose of this meeting is to decide if you are worth rehabilitating or not.
假如值得呢
And if I am?
那我会给你一份工作
Then I get you a job.
假如不值得呢
And if I'm not?
那你就再也不会见到我了
Then you never see me again.
然后等你下次再出什么意外的时候
And the next time you have an incident,
你就要被单独监禁一个月了
you will go to solitary confinement for a month.
所以我建议你回到自己的囚室
So I suggest you go back to your cell
好好想想在这里服刑期间你想做到什么
and you think long and hard about what you want to accomplish during your time here.
必须承认
I have to say,
我很高兴你们决定和解
I'm glad you've decided to settle
而不是打官司
rather than fight these suits.
如你所见  这里的情况有些紧张
Well, as you can see, things are a little tight around here,
我们处于劣势
so you have us at a disadvantage.
我只知道你们不想在接下来的六个月里
What I have is the fact that you don't want to be talking
在庭上谈论你们雇用了一个骗子这件事
about having hired a fraud in court for the next six months.
对  我们不想  所以...
No, we don't, so...
恕我直言  这不是一份提议
With all due respect, this isn't an offer,
而是一份废纸
it's a typo.
也恕我直言  这不是诉讼
And with all due respect, this isn't a lawsuit,
而是敲诈
it's a shakedown.
胡说八道
Bullshit.
这是让你们和被你们欺骗的客户们
This is a chance for you to wipe the slate clean
一笔勾销过去的机会
with the clients you defrauded.
一千万已经是很大"一笔"了
And $10 million is a hell of a goddamn wipe.
这只是罚金的十分之一而已
It's ten cents on the dollar.
你要是不接受  就一分钱都没有了
If you don't take it, it's going to be zero cents on the dollar.
你这是什么意思
What the hell are you talking about?
这笔钱是从我们合伙人的入股基金里来的
This money is from our partner buy-in fund.
是我们仅存的现金了
It's the only cash we have.
一旦合伙人们发现我们用这笔钱来和解
And once the partners find out that we're using it to settle,
他们不会善罢甘休的
they're gonna come after it.
所以你大概有一小时的时间
So you have about an hour
在落款上签名
to sign on the dotted line,
不然就永远也别想得到那笔钱
or that money's gone forever.
仔细想清楚吧  阿琳
So take a look around, Arlene,
错过这笔钱  也就没钱再给你了
'cause once it's gone, there isn't any more left.
你们蓄意诈骗自己的客户
You knowingly defrauded your own clients.
你们这是对司法系统的嘲讽
You made a mockery of the legal system.
我不会让你们免于责罚的
And I won't let you get away with it.
这么跟你说吧  阿琳
You want to know something, Arlene?
我们的确做过错事  也正为此付出代价
We did something wrong, and now we're paying for it.
但我已经有点厌倦所有人都一副
But I'm getting a little sick and tired
被迈克・罗斯坑了的样子
of people acting like Mike Ross screwed them over.
他全心全意地对待每一位客户
He gave his heart and soul to every client he ever had,
如果重审那些案件
and if those cases were reopened,
结果不会有丝毫变化
they would end up exactly in the same place.
因此  你签不签随你
So, you can sign that deal or not,
但我可不会
but I'm not gonna spend another second
在你们这些寄生虫身上浪费时间了
dealing with a parasite like you.
唐娜  哈维在哪  我有事找他
Donna, where's Harvey? I need to talk to him.
他刚谈判完
He's finishing up a negotiation.
-是急事  -怎么了  出什么事了
- This can't wait. - Why? What's going on?
我去了监狱  但他们没让我进去
I got up there and they turned me away.
这不可能  我帮你申请上了
No, that can't be. I got you on that list.
不是因为这个  他们拒绝我来访
That's not it. They turned me away
是因为他跟人打架了
because he got into a fight.
-什么  跟谁打架了  -我不知道
- What? With who? - I don't know.
就在我去探视他的时候
All I know is that I went to go and see him,
他们说他打了架
they said he got into a fight,
所以没让我进去探视
and then they wouldn't let me in.
-很好  -这算哪门子好
- Good. - How is that good?
因为如果他们不让你进
Because if they wouldn't let you in,
就证明他还手了
it means he fought back.
只是被人打了是不会被取消探视权的
You don't lose visitation if you just got jumped.
哈维  我不在乎他是否还手了
Harvey, I don't care if he fought back or not.
还手了也不代表他没事
It doesn't mean that he's okay.
瑞秋  听我说  他们有义务
Rachel, listen to me. They have an obligation
告知你他是否进了医务室
to tell you if he's in the infirmary.
他们提过他进了医务室吗
Did they tell you he was in the infirmary?
没有
No.
那好  我知道该怎么做了
Okay, then this is what I'm gonna do.
我会给监狱打电话问清来龙去脉
I'm gonna call up there and get to the bottom of this,
但这得需要点时间  所以你要有耐心
but it might take a while, so I need you to be patient.
好的
Okay.
唐娜  取消我下午的行程
Donna, cancel my afternoon
让雷五分钟之内在楼下等我
and have Ray meet me downstairs in five minutes.
我还以为你不担心迈克呢
I thought you said you weren't worried about Mike.
我那么说只是为了让她不担心
I only said that so that she wouldn't worry.
监狱取消他的探视权
They only take visitation away if you're the one
只能是因为是他挑起的事端
who starts the fight,
也就是说他出事了
which means something Goddamn happened down there
而我要查清楚究竟是怎么回事的
and I'm gonna figure out what it is.
格蕾琴  有什么事
Gretchen, what can I do for you?
我琢磨着既然大家都走了
Well, I thought since everyone was gone
我就来主管的厨房试试  换换口味
maybe I could help myself to the executive kitchen for a change.
只是想换换口味吗
For a change?
我想让你知道  我完全不知道
I wanted to let you know that I had no idea
那些人会走  不然我是绝对不会
those people were leaving or I never would have gone
-去牙医的  -我明白  格蕾琴
- to that appointment. - I know, Gretchen.
还有件事
I would also like to point out
既然大家都走了
that since they did leave,
就剩下你我  还有瑞秋・赞恩
between me, you, and Rachel Zane,
这公司女性的黑人比例可提升了一大截
this firm just got a whole lot blacker.
于我而言
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
这不会影响到任何事
that has nothing to do with anything.
格蕾琴  既然你来了
Gretchen, as long as you're here--
你想问我是否能同时兼任前台
You want to know if I can handle the reception desk
和路易斯的助理
and Louis at the same time.
你怎么知道我会问这件事
How did you know I was going to ask you that?
因为这是优秀秘书的素质
Because that's what good secretaries do.
说得没错
Sure as shit is.
大家都离职了也有一点好处
Well, there's one thing about everybody being gone.
我们三个什么时候有过机会像现在这样
When would the three of us ever find ourselves
在这里闲扯
in here just shooting the shit?
换做以前你也不会觉得这是什么好事
And when would you have thought that was a good thing?
这姑娘真是伶牙俐齿
This one is a keeper.
人家知道
I know.
对了  声明一下
Oh, and for the record,
我也是与黑人同心的
I'm black in here.
-你来干什么  -还用问
- What are you doing here? - What do you mean
我来干什么吗  我想知道出了什么事
what am I doing here? I want to know what's going on.
还能有什么事  什么事都没有
What's going on? Nothing's going on.
-我坐牢了  -什么都没发生吗
- I'm in prison. - Nothing's going on?
那你的脸是怎么回事
Then why do you look like that?
用不着你管
It is none of your business.
那现在是我主动要管
Well, I'm making it my business
因为瑞秋今早来探视你
because Rachel came to visit you this morning,
但被告知你跟人打架了
and they told her you got in a fight.
是啊  那你为什么不发挥专长
Yeah, well, why don't you do what you always do
随便编点什么  告诉她没这回事
and make up some bullshit and tell her it's not true?
因为我正忙着活下来呢
Because I'm busy trying to survive in here.
你有事为什么不告诉我
Why won't you tell me?
告诉你  你就会出面帮我解决
Because you'll try and handle it for me.
也许真该由我出面解决
Well, maybe I should be handling it for you
因为你太蠢了
because you're too stupid
蠢到第一天入狱就惹是生非
not to piss someone off on the first day.
好了  哈维  你不是想知道怎么回事吗
Okay, Harvey. You want to know what happened?
惹毛他的不是我
It wasn't me who pissed him off.
-是你  -这话什么意思
- It was you. - What are you talking about?
-弗兰克・加洛  -该死
- Frank Gallo. - Holy shit.
他怎么在这里
What's he doing in here?
不知道  我还指望你告诉我呢
I don't know. I was hoping you'd tell me that.
他因为敲诈勒索被我弄进监狱了
I put him away for racketeering.
这就说不通了
That doesn't make any sense.
我印象中  这种罪不会进这所监狱
Last time I checked, that doesn't land him in here.
没错
You're right.
加洛这种人能被关在这只有一个原因
A guy like Gallo only lands in here for one reason:
表现良好
good behavior.
你这口气怎么好像这还是好事
Why are you saying that like it's a good thing?
因为这意味着表现不良好他就不能在这儿
Because bad behavior can get him out.
-你要去哪  -去找典狱长
- Where are you going? - I'm gonna go to the warden.
告诉他前因后果
Tell him the whole story.
不用一周就能让他走人
We'll get him outta here within the week.
这就是我没告诉你的原因
That's exactly why I did not want to tell you.
这里的警卫都被收买了
Look, these guards are corrupt.
你去找典狱长  就会有人告诉加洛
You go to the warden, it gets back to Gallo,
他就会加倍来找我麻烦
he's gonna come after me twice as hard.
那也不过是一周的时间  你还有两年
It's one week instead of two years.
我们要有机会让他转狱就得把握机会
Look, we got a chance to get him outta here, I'm gonna take it.
他有瑞秋的电话号码
He's got Rachel's phone number.
那就更有理由该这么做了...
that's all the more reason to do it...
该死的  哈维
God damn it, Harvey!
你自己逼我胖揍你一顿
You pushed me to beat the shit out of you
以此证明我能在这里照顾好自己
so that you'd know I could take care of myself in here,
你现在是想让我自己解决
now are you gonna let me do that,
还是拖我的后腿
or are you gonna cut my legs out from under me?
我不插手
I'll stay out of it.
我要你保证
I want your word.
我保证不去找监狱长
I won't go to the warden.
我还在想你要什么时候才现身
I was wondering when you'd show up.
别搞得跟不认识我一样  哈维
Don't act like you don't remember me, Harvey.
你我都心知肚明你为什么来这
We both know why you're here.
我不明白你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我来这是为了见委托人
I'm here because I represent the prison.
胡扯
Bullshit.
我戳到了你的痛处  所以你才来
I pulled a string and you came.
你以为在你准备走的时候
You think it's a coincidence I'm standing here
我在这里是个巧合吗
while you're walking out?
好吧  加洛  你引起我的注意了
Okay, Gallo, you got my attention.
你想让我进去
You want me to step inside?
还是你想出来
Or you want to come out here?
我们都知道这不可能
We both know that's not possible.
你欠我的13年
You owe me 13 years.
我会收回来的
I'm gonna collect.
那个调查员
I didn't do anything to you
本来就在调查你  你也知道我并没多做什么
that that investigator didn't start and you know it.
如果他的小男友出现在这里
Well, if his little boyfriend ever shows up in here,
我也会去找他的
I'll be sure to take it up with him.
你到底想要什么  加洛
What do you want, Gallo?
我已经得到想要的了
I already have what I want.
那就是知道了每次你电话响的时候
Which is knowing that every time your phone rings,
你都要自问这通电话是不是要告诉你
you're gonna ask yourself is this the call where you find out
为你进来的那个家伙
that the guy who's in here for you
永远出不去了
is never coming out.
听着  你这个贱人
Listen to me, you son of a bitch.
你以为你进去了我就动不了你了吗
you think I can't hurt you in here?
我会悬赏你的人头
I'll put a Goddamn bounty on your head.
只要能打断你的腿  我付多少都可以
I'll pay 'em whatever it takes to break your legs.
如果这不管用
And if that doesn't work,
我就等你出来然后亲手干掉你
I'll wait till you get out and I'll kill you myself.
如果你不想这般下场
So unless you want that to happen,
就别再去惹迈克・罗斯
don't you ever even look at Mike Ross again.
铃铃电话响了  大律师
Ring, ring, counselor.
铃  铃
Ring, ring.
我就知道会在这找到你
I knew I'd find you here.
因为每次你觉得打败了某人
'Cause this is where you come
就会来这里
when you think you just beat somebody.
我能为你做什么  杰克
What can I do for you, Jack?
你可以告诉我你是用自己的钱来解决这场诉讼
You can tell me you used your own money to settle that lawsuit.
因为如果不是的话  我们就有麻烦了
'Cause if you didn't, we're gonna have a problem.
那我告诉你我们有麻烦了
Then I'd say we have a problem.
该死的  你用了入股金
God damn it. You used the buy-in fund.
是的  我用了
Yes, we did.
那样的话
Then I guess...
我们法庭见了
I'll see you in court.
你要起诉我个人
You're suing me personally?
-门上写的是你的名字  -杰克
- It's your name on the door. - Jack.
我知道公司结构从来不是你的强项
I know corporate structures were never your strong suit,
所以我要给你解释解释
so I'm gonna explain something to you.
我们虽然用"合伙人"这个词
We may use the word "Partnership,"
但这是个有限责任公司
but this is a LLC.
这世上没有一个法官
And no judge in the world
会让你打破这个规矩的
is going to let you pierce that corporate veil.
当他们知道你雇了个冒牌货时就会了
They will once they learn you knowingly hired a fraud.
这二者毫无关系
One has nothing to do with the other.
即便你真的找到了这样的法官
And if you really did find a judge who would do that,
那你也早带着一卡车的律师来了
then you'd be here with an army of lawyers and a Brinks truck
而不是汗涔涔的小手握着一张破纸
instead of standing alone with a flimsy piece of paper
独自一人站在这儿
in your sweaty little hands.
你再嘴硬也没有  杰西卡
You can talk tough all you want, Jessica.
实际上  我的确有一卡车律师而你没有
The fact is, I do have an army of lawyers and you don't.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我最后还是在罗伯特・赞恩那找了份工作
I took that job with Robert Zane after all.
我愿意把这一战打下去
And I'm willing to drag this fight out,
这就看你了
so the choice is yours.
把我们的钱还给我们  或者破产倒闭
Give us our money or go out of business.
我可以跟你聊两句吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
聊什么
About what?
牢房本该是让你觉得安全的地方
Listen, a man's cell should be the one place he can feel safe.
我把你的这个权利剥夺了  我很抱歉
I took that away from you, and I'm sorry.
没错  但对不起在这管个屁用
Yeah, well, sorry doesn't do shit for me in here.
我知道
I know.
所以我想弥补错误
That's why I want to make it up to you.
你逗我玩吧
Are you kidding me?
我现在这个状况就是一个电话搞的
That's exactly what got me in this situation in the first place.
我知道
I know that.
但我也知道你今天早上
But I also know you wanted to call
想给某个人打电话
whoever you wanted to call this morning.
我想帮你  跟你和解
And I'm trying to make it up to you.
这玩意和解不了
Yeah, well, this doesn't do that.
听着  光是让你知道我有这玩意
Hey, look, I can get in a lot of trouble
就能让我惹一身麻烦
for just letting you know I have this.
你为什么不干点别的来惹麻烦呢
Why don't you do something else that can get you into trouble?
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
告诉他们加洛贿赂警卫让你换房间
Tell them that Gallo paid the guards to have you switch.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
对  因为你怕他
Yeah, because you're afraid of him.
你说的太他妈对了
You're damn straight I am.
最重要的是
And on top of that,
我会成为这里的众矢之的
I'd make a permanent enemy of everyone else in here,
因为在这地方  最招麻烦的名头
because the worst thing you can be known for, my man,
就是告密
is as someone who would do something like that.
也就是说我得自己对付这个人
Which means I get to deal with this all by myself.
没事  你可以坐在这
It's all right, you can stay.
他走不走无所谓
It doesn't matter if he stays or goes,
我跟你没什么可说的
I got nothing to say to you.
没事  因为我有要跟你说的
That's okay, 'cause I got something to say to you.
想知道来了这里后我最喜欢什么时候吗
You want to know what my favorite time of day is in here?
就是现在
It's right now.
有电视看
Got the TV going.
兄弟们坐在那里打牌讲笑话
Guys are sitting around playing cards, telling jokes.
能让人几乎忘掉是在监狱里
You almost forget you're in prison,
这就是我为什么过来
which is why I came over here.
因为我要保证让你永远忘不了
'Cause I want to make sure you never forget.
总有一天
There's gonna come a time
当这里没这么多人
when this place isn't filled with people,
只有你我两个人的时候
and you and I are alone.
连你哥们哈维・斯佩克特
Then all those vicious threats
今天对我的那番恶意威胁
your boy Harvey Specter made to me today
也救不了你
aren't gonna save you.
听说兰德-考德-赞恩律所今天过得不错
I heard today was a good day for Rand, Kaldor, Zane.
如果你是指我雇佣杰克・索罗夫的部门
If this is about me hiring Jack Soloff's department,
我这么做不是为了和你作对
I didn't do it to stick it to you.
-反正他们都要离开了  -也许吧
- They were leaving anyway. - Maybe.
但如果你的第一步
But if your first move
就是让他们来要回合伙人的钱
is to have them come after their partner money,
那我一定误解了我们之前的友好关系
then I must have been wrong that we were on good terms.
杰西卡  我是接受了你的道歉
Jessica, I accepted your apology.
我觉得这并不等于我们很要好
I wouldn't say that makes us on good terms.
但他找你要钱可不是我指使的
But I had nothing to do with him coming after your money.
那是你和他的事
That's between you and him.
但你有能力阻止他
But you do have the power to stop it.
但我不喜欢指挥我的新员工的
And I am not in the habit of telling my brand new employees
一举一动
what they can and can't do.
你这次不喜欢也得干
Well, I need you to do it anyway.
杰西卡
Jessica--
罗伯特
Robert...
我需要你这么做
I need this.
我知道对合伙人指手画脚
And I know it's not your style
不是你的风格
to tell your partners what to do,
但如果你不这样做的话
but if you don't make it your style,
我就死定了
I'm dead in the water.
我是哈维・斯佩克特
This is Harvey Specter.
丹伯里联邦监狱有人向你致电
You have a call from Danbury Federal Prison.
-你愿意承担费用吗  -愿意
- Do you accept the charges? - Yes.
我不理解你的回答
I do not understand your response.
-我说愿意  -请回答是或否
- Yes. God damn it. - Please respond yes or no.
是
Yes.
-喂  -迈克  感谢上帝
- Hello. - Mike, thank God.
感谢他什么
Thank God what?
你看着我的眼睛
You looked me in the eye
跟我保证你不会管的
and you said you would stay out of it.
结果连停车场都没走到
You couldn't even make it to the parking lot
-就去威胁加洛了  -迈克  你听我说
- without threatening Gallo? - Mike, listen to me.
我不听  你还要继续骗我吗
No, what, so you can lie to me again?
还是说你要告诉我你没有去威胁他
Or are you gonna tell me you didn't do that?
我那么做不是因为我觉得
Look, I didn't do it because I didn't think
你处理不了
you could handle yourself.
我威胁他是因为他惹到我了
I did it because he got under my skin.
我才不管你是为什么这么做的
I don't give a shit why you did it.
你发誓说你不会这么做的
You swore you wouldn't.
但你现在把这事弄得更糟糕了
Instead, you've made things worse.
哈维  如果我连你都没法信任
Harvey, if I can't even trust you,
那我在这儿才真是没戏了
then I do not stand a chance in here.
我现在没法跟你说话
Look, I can't talk right now.
什么叫你现在没法说话
What do you mean you can't talk?
瑞秋现在正我办公室里盯着我看
Rachel's in my office looking at me right now
再过五秒她肯定起疑出了什么事
and she's gonna think something's wrong in five seconds,
所以除非你改变主意想让我告诉她了
so unless you've changed your mind about me not telling her,
否则我得挂了
I gotta go.
哈维  你得把她的电话拿走
Harvey, you gotta get the phone from her.
好的  瑞克  没问题
Sure, Rick, no problem.
-哈维  拿走她的电话  -八点半没问题
- Harvey, get the phone from her. - 8:30 sounds great.
第一轮你请
First round's on you.
瑞秋  正好你在
Rachel, good, you're here.
我正好找你呢
I was just gonna come see you.
你没联系我  所以我想着
I didn't hear from you, so I just figured--
他没事  是系统出错了
He's good. There was an error in the paperwork.
出事的犯人不是他  刚好同姓而已
It's a different inmate, same last name.
好的  那我明天就能见他了
Okay. So I can see him tomorrow.
其实  他说希望你给他点时间
Actually, he asked that you give him a little time.
-什么  -瑞秋  监狱对他是个大改变
- What? - Rachel, prison is a big adjustment.
过两周他就能适应点了
He'll be ready in about two weeks.
那为什么他给我发了五十多条短信
So then, why do I have about 50 texts from him
跟我说他等不及要见我了
saying that he can't wait to see me?
-什么  -哈维  到底怎么回事
- What? - Harvey, what's going on?
-手机给我  -不给
- Give me the phone. - No.
-我说把手机给我  -除非告诉我怎么回事
- I said give me the phone. - I'm not giving you anything
否则就不给你
until you tell me what's going on.
那些短信不是迈克发的
Those texts aren't from Mike.
那是谁发的
Then who are they from?
是我当检察官的时候抓的一个人发的
From a guy I put away when I was an ADA.
天哪
Oh, my God.
瑞秋  别自己吓自己
Rachel, don't let your imagination run wild.
-没事的  -你怎么知道
- It's gonna be okay. - You don't know that
-进监狱的又不是你  -没错  不是我
- because you're not in there. - You're right, I'm not.
那你打算怎么办
Then what the hell are you gonna do about it?
我打算按我答应迈克的办
I'm gonna do what I promised Mike.
那就是相信他能处理好
I'm gonna have faith that he can handle it.
真不敢相信  你打算袖手旁观吗
I don't believe it. So you're not gonna do anything?
你以为我不想马上救他出来吗
You think I don't want to bust him outta there right now?
如果我想了办法又没成功
Look, if I try and do something and it doesn't work,
他会更难处理
it makes it worse for him.
-那人暴力吗  -瑞秋
- Is he violent? - Rachel--
-那人暴力吗  -我保证了他
- Is he violent? - I made him a promise--
我不管你保证了什么
I don't give a shit.
他进去是为了保护你
He's in there to protect you,
所以你最好想个办法保护好他
so you better figure out a way to protect him
否则我告诉你  哈维
because Goddamn it, Harvey,
要是他在里面出了什么事
if something happens to him in there
你又袖手旁观
and you didn't do anything,
我绝对不会原谅你的
I will never forgive you.
哈维  我知道你用不着我来告诉你
Harvey, I know you don't need me to tell you this,
但她是对的
but she's right,
如果迈克真出了什么事
because if something actually does happen to Mike,
就算她原谅了你
even if she forgives you,
你也不会原谅自己的
you're never gonna forgive yourself.
什么事  哈维
What do you want, Harvey?
只要你五分钟
Five minutes of your time and that's all.
要五分钟是聊天  还是找我帮忙
Five minutes to catch up, or five minutes to ask a favor?
要你五分钟  帮我保护迈克・罗斯
Five minutes to help me protect Mike Ross.
怎么保护  如果我没记错
Protect him how? 'Cause last time I checked,
他现在好像进了监狱吧
he was in the bosom of the federal penitentiary system.
肖恩  他和我抓的一个人被关在一起
Sean, he's in there with a guy I put away
那人可不是吃素的
and the guy is no joke.
我很遗憾  哈维
I'm sorry to hear that, Harvey.
但你要我做什么
But what am I supposed to do?
我要你把那个人转到别的监狱
You're supposed to move the guy to another prison.
我没权力这么做
I don't have the authority to do that and you know that.
你能想办法弄到这个权力
You can get the authority.
你可是联邦检察官
You're a federal prosecutor.
那你为什么不直接去找
Then why the hell don't you go after the prosecutor
起诉迈克的检察官
that put Mike away in the first place?
因为她不欠我什么  你欠我
'Cause she doesn't owe me, and you do.
我们合作那么久的时间里
You got a lot of balls saying that to me
你一直都知道他是冒牌货
when the entire time we were working together,
居然还敢来跟我说这话
you knew the kid was a fraud.
那个孩子帮你扳倒了
That kid helped you take down
查尔斯・傅滋曼和埃里克・伍德尔
Charles Forstman and Eric Woodall
让你有了名气
and put you on the map.
出名  别扯了
The map? Bullshit.
认识你们俩之前我就很有名
I was on the map long before I met either of you.
你是想告诉我那次定罪没让你
You're going to tell me you haven't shot up the ranks
青云直上吗
since that conviction?
哈维  你刚进来的时候
You know, Harvey, when you first walked in here,
我还以为你是因为骗了我这么久
for a second I actually thought you were gonna apologize
而向我道歉
for lying to me all that time.
我不需要你的原谅  肖恩
I don't need your forgiveness, Sean.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
好吧  我想想办法
All right, I'll see what I can do.
但是  哈维
But, Harvey,
现在是你欠我了
now you owe me one.
杰克
Jack?
我今天很累  你来这里做什么
I've had a long day. What are you doing here?
你知道我来做什么
You know what I'm doing here.
你去找罗伯特・赞恩  让他制止了我们
You went to Robert Zane and you had him shut us down.
我只是做了必须要做的
I did what I had to do.
我要走了
Now if you'll excuse me.
我只是想要回我的钱而已
All I wanted was my money back.
你越早接受钱已经没有了的事实
Well, the sooner you get used to the fact that it's gone,
我们就能越快重回各自生活的正轨
the sooner we can both move on with our lives.
这就是问题所在  我回不了
That's the problem. I can't move on with my life.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我付不起赞恩的买入金
I can't afford Zane's buy-in.
什么
What?
这怎么可能
How is that possible?
杰西卡  听我说
Jessica, listen to me.
虽然你知道哈德曼知道我做了什么
You know what I did that Hardman found out about,
但你不知道的是我为什么要那么做
but what you don't know is why I did it.
我需要那笔钱
I needed the money.
现在你想让我拿自己的钱
And now you want me to give you your money back
来还你吗
out of my own pocket?
杰西卡  拜托
Jessica, please.
这是我重新开始的机会
This is a chance for me to have a new start.
即使我想帮你  我也不能这么做
Even if I wanted to, I can't do that.
-为什么  -你知道为什么
- Why not? - You know why not.
我自掏腰包
I pay you out of my own pocket.
就是自己排除了对公司有限责任的特权
I'm piercing that corporate veil myself.
要是合伙人知道了  我会赔上几百万的
And if the partners find out, it will cost me millions.
他们不会知道的
They won't find out.
我不能冒这个险
Well, I can't take that chance.
杰西卡  我需要这笔钱
Jessica, I need this.
对不起  杰克
I'm sorry, Jack.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
早上好
Morning.
怎么了
What?
你知道怎么了
You know what.
我牙齿上有东西吗
Do I have something in my teeth?
没有  但是你脑子有问题
No, but you got some bullshit in your brain.
-什么  -"这里是黑的"
- Excuse me? - "Black in here."
拜托  我见过的女人没人能比你白
Please, you're the whitest woman I ever met.
是吗
Is that a fact?
那你倒是说说看
Tell me something different.
耳听为虚  眼见为实
How about I show you something different?
-那不是...  -是的
- Is that... - Yep.
-你肯定在逗我  -没有
- You gotta be kidding me. - Nope.
-那是哪一年  -96年
- What year was that? - '96.
-你们交往了多久  -七个月
- How long were you together? - Seven months.
信了吧  看不惯夫人
That that, Mrs. Hater.
他上一张专辑之前还是之后
Before his last album or after?
你以为那首歌是写的谁
Who do you think that song was about?
该死  "这里是黑的"
Shit. "Black in here."
简直全身都是黑的
She's black all over.
很高兴我们能达成一致
I'm glad we came to an agreement.
我通常是不向
And it's usually not my habit
对方律师献殷勤的
to court a dalliance with opposing counsel,
不过我注意到
but I couldn't help but notice
你手上没戴戒指
you don't have a ring on your finger.
想都别想  利特先生
Not in a million years, Mr. Litt.
请回你的位置
Go back to your own side.
对于一个如此主动的男人  你至少得...
Man puts himself out there, the least you can do is...
关于针对皮尔逊  斯佩克特和利特的集体诉讼案
Regarding the class action against Pearson, Specter, Litt,
双方都同意和解条款吗
do both parties agree to the terms of the settlement?
-是的  法官  -我们也是  法官
- We do, Your honor. - We do as well, Your Honor.
如果没有人持有异议
Then unless there are any objections,
本庭将批准...
I see no reason for this court not to ratify--
我有异议  法官
I have an objection, Your Honor.
-什么  -你是
- What? - And you are?
他是艾略特・斯坦普尔  法官
His name is A. Elliott Stemple, Your Honor,
他无权参与此案
and he has no standing in this case.
利特先生
Mr. Litt.
我是没有权利  法官
I have no standing, Your Honor.
但我代表罗斯曼保险公司
But I represent Rothman Insurance,
本公司虽不是本集体诉讼案的客户
a company not included in the class of clients
但同样由这个故意雇了一位骗子的律所代理
misrepresented by a firm that knowingly hired a fraud.
没有任何证据能够证明我们故意做了什么
There's not one shred of proof we knowingly did anything.
但是有证据证明你们雇了一位骗子
But there is proof that you employed a fraud,
这也是你们要和罗森小姐
which is why you're settling with Ms. Rosen
进行和解的原因
in the first place.
-你们一伙的吗  -开什么玩笑
- Are you in on this? - Are you kidding me?
好了  斯坦普尔先生  呈上你的证据
All right, Mr. Stemple. Submit your evidence.
明天本庭将给出判决
The court will rule on it tomorrow.
我们虽然同意以十分之一的金额进行和解
We may have agreed to ten cents on the dollar,
但要是这事儿黄了
but if this goes south,
我们会拿走你们的每一分钱
we're coming after you for every penny you've got.
你这个混蛋
You little son of a bitch.
说话小心点  利特  这里是法庭
Watch it, Litt. We're in a court of law.
我才不管这是哪  是杰克・索罗夫让你来的
I don't care where we are. Jack Soloff put you up to this,
-我知道  -那又怎样
- and I know it. - So what?
那么我就会证明
So I'm gonna prove it.
一旦法官知道你做了什么
And when the judge realizes what you did,
他就会让你进监狱
he's gonna throw your ass in jail.
是吗
Really? Huh.
因为在我看来  法官会证明我的客户是
Because the way I see it, the judge is gonna certify
这个集体诉讼案的一员  因为不管杰克
that my client is a member of this class because they are one
有没有告诉我他们都是一体的
whether Jack tipped me off to them or not.
到时候  合同失效
And when that happens, I kill the deal,
你们就要把钱
and your money goes back to
还给所有的合伙人
the partners that you took it from.
所以  你何不拖着你这两只肥腿
So, why don't you march your fat feet
回到那仅剩两位律师的
back to the only two lawyers left
悲剧小律所
at that miserable little firm
然后想想要怎么倾家荡产
and decide just how deep you're gonna reach
来还我的钱
into your own pockets to pay me off.
因为在我看来
Because as I see it, phew,
一天后你们将失去一切
you have about 24 hours until you lose everything.
你又想干嘛  哈维
What do you want now, Harvey?
我想就加洛的事向你道歉
I wanted to apologize for what happened with Gallo.
那样是不对的
It was wrong.
根本就不应该发生  我很抱歉
Shouldn't have happened, and I'm sorry.
但是呢
But?
但是我不在乎我给你承诺了什么
But I don't care what I promised you
因为我找到了一个方法让他离开这里
because I found a way to get him out of here,
我也要这么做
and I'm gonna take it.
我告诉过你  如果你去找典狱长...
I told you, you go to the warden--
我不是要去找典狱长  我去找了肖恩・卡荷尔
I'm not going to the warden. I went to Sean Cahill.
这意味着在他们给他带上
Which means Gallo won't know about it
镣铐让滚回他该待的地方之前
until they're putting shackles on him
加洛是不会知道的
to take him back to wherever the hell he came from.
有什么是你没告诉我的
What are you not telling me?
我让他以敲诈罪的名义进了监狱
I put him away for racketeering.
但这并不是他真正的罪行
But that's not what he really did.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我们发现他参与了谋杀案
We had him for conspiracy to commit murder.
但是警方就让他认罪的那个视频
And the police let the tape of that bastard admitting
落在了证据链外二十分钟
that he did it out of the chain of custody
导致证据无效
for 20 minutes.
所以你转而以敲诈勒索来来追究他的责任
So you went after him for racketeering instead.
我用了三个
I used every trick I had to put him away
最多五年的罪名
for 15 years for three crimes
让他被判了15年
that would have added to five years at the most.
所以他那么恨你
And that's why he hates you so much.
这也是我把他从这弄走之前
It's also why I need you to lay low
需要你低调一点的原因
until I can get him out of here.
这我能理解  哈维
Oh, I can appreciate that, Harvey,
但我没法整天都躲在我自己的牢房里
but I can't exactly hide in my cell 24 hours a day.
那么我建议你反其道而行之
Then I suggest you do the complete opposite.
你知道吗  我一般不接待没有预约的人
You know, I don't normally take walk-ins.
抱歉
Sorry.
不过你既然来了
Well, as long as you're here.
我想过了  然后
Well, I thought about it, and...
我希望有份工作
I'd like a job.
并且如果不是太麻烦的话
And if it's not too much trouble,
我希望尽可能出现在人多的地方
I'd like it to be in front of as many people as possible.
为什么希望如此呢
And why is that?
在人群中我更容易不去招惹是非
It'll be easier for me to stay out of trouble in a crowd.
很好
Good.
因为我在厨房给你安排了一份工作
Because I got you a job in the kitchen.
谢谢
Thank you.
别谢我  谢你自己就行了
Don't thank me. Thank yourself.
如果你没有冲进来见我
If you hadn't come in to see me,
我永远不会和你说这事的
I never would have told you about it.
是真的吗
Is that true?
你真的不接待没有预约的人吗
You don't really take walk-ins?
才不是
Nah.
只是说说而已
Just something to say.
账单记录就在那里
The billing records are right there.
迈克当时出席了会议
Mike was at the meeting.
该死  你说对了  他抓到我们的把柄了
Shit, you're right. He's got us.
-你知道这代表着什么  -我知道
- You know what this means. - I do.
路易  我刚收到你的信息
Louis, I just got your message.
-发生什么事了  -哈维  我们有麻烦了
- What's going on? - Harvey, we got a problem,
而且你不会喜欢的
and you're not going to like it.
艾略特・斯坦普尔与一个
Elliott Stemple showed up in court
被集体诉讼除名的公司一起出现在了法庭上
with an excluded member of the class.
艾略特・斯坦普尔  你在开玩笑吗
Elliott Stemple? Are you kidding me?
他伏击了我  哈维  法官正准备
He ambushed me, Harvey. The judge was about to ratify
批准和解方案  他不知道从哪冒了出来
the settlement when he comes out of nowhere.
你让我怎么办
What was I supposed to do?
证明他的委托人不在集体诉讼的原告里
You prove his client isn't part of the class,
然而把这事情给压下去
and you shut this thing down.
不行  他的委托人的确是集体诉讼原告之一
I can't do that because his client is a part of the class.
-什么  那不可能  -是的  就是这样
- What? That's not possible. - Yes, it is.
迈克和罗斯曼保险公司有过一次会面
Mike took one meeting with Rothman Insurance.
杰克・索罗夫把这事告诉了斯坦普尔
Jack Soloff told Stemple about it.
-不可能  -都在这了  哈维
- No way. - It's all right here, Harvey.
而且如果我们今晚不付钱给他
And if we don't pay him off tonight,
明天他就不会接受这个条件了
he kills that deal tomorrow
而我们十分钟后就要停业了
and we're out of business ten minutes later.
狗屁  那是敲诈勒索
Bullshit. That's blackmail.
我是不会向敲诈勒索屈服的
I'm not giving in to blackmail.
拜托  你觉得我想这么做吗
Oh, come on, do you think I want to do this?
他捏着我们的命根子  哈维
He's got us by the balls, Harvey.
如果我们不付钱给他  那么那天晚上我们
If we don't pay him, what was everything we went through
经历的一切意义何在呢
the other night even for?
这就意味着现在  我们只需要搞清楚
Which means right now, we just have to figure out
我们愿意付多少钱
how much we're willing to pay.
不  我们不
No, we don't.
哈维  你在说什么
Harvey, what are you saying?
我在说斯坦普尔根本不在乎你们两个
I'm saying Stemple doesn't care about you two.
他只是想和我共处一室看我大出血
He just wants to get in a room with me and see me bleed.
你不能自掏腰包付钱给那个人
You are not paying that man out of your pocket.
-是的  就是这样  -哈维  杰西卡说得对
- Yes, I am. - Harvey, Jessica's right.
不  她说的不对
No, she's not.
我们都知道是我把大家带进这趟浑水的
We all know I got us into this mess.
是时候由我来把我们大家带出来了
It's time for me to get us out of it.
好吧  你想跟他正面交锋  没问题
All right, you want him, you got him.
但你会恨不得把他的头给扯下来
But you're gonna be tempted to rip that man's head off,
而当那种情况出现时  你得克制住
and when that happens, you're not going to do that.
你要付钱给他
You're going to pay him.
然后你就让他从这里滚出去
And then you're going to throw his sorry ass out of here.
哈维  有空聊一下吗
Harvey, do you have a minute?
说快点就有  等下还要见个人
If it's quick. Someone's on their way over.
我想就之前的事跟你道歉
I want to apologize to you about earlier.
你不需要这么做
You don't need to do that.
是的  我需要
Yes, I do.
我知道你在按你觉得最好的方式行事
I know that you're doing what you feel is best.
我只是
I just...
我之前没想到这事会有那么难
I didn't think this was going to be as hard as it is.
对我来说也一样
For me too.
而且不管怎么样
And for what it's worth,
我接受你的建议
I took your advice.
我会把那家伙从那儿弄走
I'm gonna get that guy out of there.
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋
Rachel?
他不会有事的
He's gonna be okay.
对于我刚刚在大厅里看到的
Aren't you getting a little long in the tooth
那位美女来说你年纪是不是大了点
for that hottie I just saw in the hall?
开始吧  斯坦普尔  我没心情和你废话
Let's get to it, Stemple, because I'm not in the mood.
多少钱
How much?
什么多少钱
How much what?
要多少钱才能让我保留我的律所
How much to let me have my firm?
你是不是想说我来这里
Do you mean to imply that I'm simply here
就是为了敲你竹杠的
on a mission to extort you?
我们都知道你是来拿我的钱的
Oh, we both know you're here to get my money
这样你就能跟杰克・索罗夫分赃了
so you can split it with Jack Soloff.
你这么小瞧我真让我感到愤慨
I resent that you think so little of me.
你是在说那不是你来这里的原因吗
You saying that's not why you're here?
我是在说我不在乎你的钱
I'm saying I don't give a shit
或者杰克・索罗夫
about your money or Jack Soloff.
我想要你的一部分
I want a piece of you.
把你的臭手从那上面挪开
Get your Goddamn hands off that.
哈维  哈维  哈维  放轻松
Harvey, Harvey, Harvey. Relax.
我来这里不是为了把我温柔的双手
I didn't come here to put my gentle hands
放在你宝贵的篮球上的
on your precious balls.
我来这里是为了拿走某样贵重的多的东西
I came here to take something far more valuable.
因为我想要的是那幅该死的鸭子画
'Cause what I want is that piece of shit duck painting.
什么
What?
就那边那幅
That right there.
我猜对了
I was right.
如果那幅画对你不重要  你早就
If that didn't mean something to you, you would have
从椅子上跳起来跟我说没问题了
jumped right out of your chair and said okay to me.
-斯坦普尔  听着  -更不用说
- Stemple, listen-- - Not to mention,
你从我认识你那天起就一直挂着那幅画
you've had that thing as long as I've known you,
而且除非是那副画对你意味着一切  不然
and there's no way a guy like you has a painting like that
像你这样的人是绝对不会挂那样一幅画的
unless it means everything to him.
你要多少钱  斯坦普尔
How much money, Stemple?
因为你是不会得到那副画的
Because you are not getting that painting.
-一千万美元  -艾略特
- $10 million. - Elliott.
-一千五百万  -该死的
- 15 million. - Goddamn it.
两千万  你还想继续吗
20 million. Do you want to keep going?
或者说你想好了吗  因为10秒钟之后
Or have you had enough? Because in ten seconds,
我要么拿两千万走人
I am walking out of here with $20 million
要么拿走那个东西
or that thing in my hands.
不然明早  我就把你的律所置于死地
Or tomorrow morning, I'm putting your firm in the ground.
画是你的了
Take the painting.
我知道你不相信我  但是你看谁来了
I know you don't trust me, but look who's headed this way.
他们过来  大家都要离开
On top of that, people are leaving.
你也应该马上走
You should leave, too.
不  那是他想要的
No. That's what he wants.
他想让我离开去一个
He wants me to go somewhere
警卫看不到我的地方
where those guards don't have a view of me.
而且就我知道的  他派你来让我走
And for all I know, he sent you to help him.
你根本不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
走开
Leave me alone.
你好  迈克
Hey there, Mike.
你在看什么  《局外人》
What you reading? "Outliers"?
我不知道你认为将要发生什么  弗兰克
I don't know what you think is gonna happen here, Frank,
但我不会让你骗我离开这个房间
but I'm not gonna let you trick me into leaving this room.
我不需要骗你  这房间就挺好
I don't need to trick you. This room will do just fine.
是吗  那你把这句话
Oh, yeah? Why don't you tell that
跟坐在我后面的两个警卫说
to the two guards sitting behind me?
你指的是那两个让我进你牢房的警卫
You mean the ones who let me into your cell?
他们去抽烟了  迈克
They took a little cigarette break, Mike.
等等  等等  等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
所以就这样吗
So that's it?
你打算让这些人杀了我
You're gonna let these guys kill me?
谁说要杀你了
Who said anything about killing you?
我们只是想弄伤你一点  或者很多
We're just gonna hurt you a little, or a lot.
不不不不不  我想说的是
No, no, no, no, no. What I meant was,
你真的胆小到不敢自己面对我
are you really too much of a pussy to take me on by yourself?
你觉得就因为你激了我几句
You think they won't come at you
他们就不会打你了吗
just because you called me out?
不  我想男人都愿意听领导的
Oh, no, I think that men respond to leaders.
你要是太害怕收拾我这样的男人
And if you're too afraid to take on a guy like me,
那你这领导当不久了
you're not gonna be a leader for much longer.
好吧  硬汉
Okay, tough guy.
你想跟我一对一  来吧
You want me one-on-one, you got it.
一个小事  我打算用这个
One little thing: I'm gonna use this
-而他们会按住你  -不不不
- and they're gonna hold you. - No, no, no!
怎么回事
What's going on here?
什么  没事
Huh? What? Nothing.
你也说没事吗
You have the same story?
对
Yeah.
对  什么事都没有
Yeah, nothing's going on here.
那你们三个离他远点
Then why don't you three get away from him,
回你们的牢房去
and go to your cells?
今天晚上我不想看见你们三个
And I don't want to see you back in here
再回这里
for the rest of the night.
我刚才看见斯坦普尔从这离开
I just saw Stemple walking out of here...
手里拿着一幅画跟
with a canvas that looks about the same size
你墙上那块空的大小一样
as that empty space on your wall.
他不会回来了
He won't be back.
所以结束了
So it's done?
结束了
It's done.
哈维
Harvey?
我记得你跟我说过那幅画
I remember you told me that painting
是你跟你妈妈唯一的快乐回忆
was the one happy memory you had of your mother before--
像我说的  杰西卡
Like I said, Jessica,
我把大家带入麻烦
I was the one who got us into this mess.
我就必须帮大家摆脱麻烦
I'm the one who needed to get us out of it.
搞定了
It's done.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
所以  你想叫哈维出来
So, you want to go get Harvey?
一起去喝一杯庆祝一下
Have a drink and celebrate?
哈维需要一个人待着  路易
Harvey needs to be alone right now, Louis.
那你跟我去
How about you and me?
我想去
I would,
但是我需要去办一件事
but there's something I need to take care of.
我明白
I understand.
路易  你的想法是对的
Louis, you had the right idea.
但方法错了
The wrong execution.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是如果我们想看起来像个律所
I mean, if we're going to look like a real firm,
那么从明早开始  我们需要
then starting tomorrow, we need to do something
把这些办公室转租出去
about subletting these offices.
我会处理
I'll take care of it.
我能问你一个问题吗
Can I ask you something?
没问题
Sure.
你为什么带警卫一起回来
Why'd you come back with the guard?
现在加洛知道是你了
Now Gallo knows it was you.
不论怎样他都会知道是我的
He would have found out it was me anyway.
但我可能不会知道
But I might not have.
我那么做不是为了让你原谅我
I didn't do it to get you to forgive me.
我那么做是因为我
I did it 'cause I never should have
当初就不该让他进来
let him in here in the first place.
笑什么
What?
我才发现我都还不知道你的名字
I just realized that I don't even know your name.
凯文
Kevin.
凯文・米勒
Kevin Miller.
迈克・罗斯
Mike Ross.
谢谢你  凯文
Thank you, Kevin.
关灯了  男士们
Lights out, gentlemen.
罗伯特  我能跟你说几句话吗
Robert, can I talk to you for a second?
说吧  你需要什么
Yeah, what do you need?
我刚才发现我不能
I just found out I'm not going to be able
进律所当合伙人了
to buy in as a partner.
-什么  -我没有那么多钱
- What? - I don't have the money.
而且我在想
And I was wondering--
我不需要一个五十岁的初级律师  杰克
I don't need a 50-year-old associate, Jack.
我知道
I know that.
如果你能让我用薪水付入股的钱
If you could just let me pay it off out of my salary.
你知道我的  我如果这么做了
You know as well as I do,if I let you do that
我就等着所有人都跟我这么要求吧
I might as well waive to buy in for everyone
求你了  罗伯特
Please,Robert.
你为什么不能贷款
Why can't you get a loan for it?
他可以
He can,
但是会有点麻烦
but it's gonna be a little complicated.
因为我打算先贷款给你
Because I'm actually loaning you this money.
你再贷款给他
And you're gonna loan it to him,
这样即使如果没人还钱
and if nobody ever repays anybody,
也没关系
nobody's gonna give a shit.
你为什么要这么做  杰西卡
Why are you doing this,Jessica?
因为是我把你带入这个麻烦的
Because I'm the one that got you into this mess.
我应该帮你摆脱它
I should be the one to get you out.
谢谢
Thank you.
其实吧  杰克
The truth is, Jack,
人越老
the older I get,
就越想多交朋友
the more I'd rather have friends out there
而不是敌人
than enemies.